

Don Osborne UX Design & Management

Based in Los Angeles, CA 323.356.9742 don@humanfriendlydesign.com humanfriendlydesign.com

Background

I'm Don Osborne, a highly experienced and award winning UX design leader with over 15 years of experience creating intuitive, user-centered designs that drive business success. I've managed designers from around the world and strive to bring out the best in my team members.

Experience

Green Dot | Principle UI Developer → UX Design Manger → Director of UX Design

- Lead UX team in design and launch of GO2bank mobile apps and account website.
- · Oversaw design of all new product features such as secured credit card, overdraft protection, savings account, Experian credit boost, help center, and bill pay.
- Managed updates to Green Dot, Walmart MoneyCard and RushCard accounts.
- Creator and maintainer of the design systems used across all Green Dot apps and websites. Lead designer for white label partner products launching in 2023.
- Managed a team of UX designers in the US and Shanghai, making user research and accessibility a key focus of the design group.

Tenable | Senior UX Designer

Sept 2017 - Dec 2018

- Designed UX/UI for Tenable's next generation network security vulnerability management in Tenable.io.
- Designed UX/UI for Lumin, a breakthrough cyber exposure visualization product.
- Designed widgets and dashboards with rich visualizations for use across Tenable's suite of products.
- Contributed to Hive Design System as part of complete product portfolio redesign.

Green Dot | Senior UX Designer → UX Design Manager

May 2015 - Sept 2017

- Designed & developed the Flex Web Design System, a front-end web framework for all Green Dot brands, seen on greendot.com, gobank.com, moneypak.com, greendotmoney.com, attheregister.com, simplypaid.com.
- Managed concept pitches for Apple Pay Cash, which Green Dot ultimately provided the services for.
- Contributed to redesign of all Green Dot brand apps for Web, iOS and Android.

Rovi | Web UI Designer → Senior User Interface Engineer

Nov 2012 - May 2015

- Designed & developed RoviGuide, a TV set top box prototype (winner of Multichannel News Innovator Award), Tilden, a HTML based European TV guide, and TotalTV, a HTML based web app built for embedding into cable and media sites.
- Utilized responsive design methodology for all products, optimizing for Mobile/Tablet/Desktop/TV sizes.

Fidelis Education | User Experience Designer

Nov 2011 - Nov 2012

- Designed FidelisEducation.com sign up/sign in, student home page, student profile, messaging system, notifications system, activity stream, account settings, job placement search panel and course work application.
- Translated mockups to working prototypes using HTML/CSS/Javascript.

CitizenGlobal | Product Manager & User Interface Designer

Apr 2010 - Nov 2011

- Designed UX & UI for admin panel, media manager, video uploader, desktop video uploader, user accounts, online video editor, WikiCG iOS App, WikiCG Android App and Facebook app.
- Productized requests from Management, Services and Support through user stories, wireframes and mockups.
- Managed developers in an Agile environment.

Engine Room | Visual Effects Editor, Web Designer & Developer

Sept 2007 - Apr 2010

- Digitized, organized and output all footage entering and leaving facility.
- Managed VFX shots in Shotgun and assigned shots to artists.
- Designed & developed engineroomhollywood.com and enginedesign.tv, creating compression workflows for web video archive system.
- Implemented HTML5 video playback and Wordpress as a news publishing system.
- $\bullet \ \, {\sf Designed/developed\ radarhollywood.com, incorporating\ user\ registration, user\ profile\ management, and}$ admin search panel.

310 Casting Studios | Tech Manager, Video Editor, Web Designer & Developer

May 2006 - Sept 2007

- Designed & developed 310castingstudios.com.
- Administered live video uploads for casting sessions.
- Trained and managed camera operators on cameras, computers, editing software and web video uploads.

In Sync Advertising | Assistant Editor, Web Designer and Systems Administrator

2/2005 - 5/2006

- Designed and developed client video review web site.
- Digitized, organized and output all footage entering and leaving facility.
- Created video compression workflows for web and DVD.
- Managed all facility editing hardware/software, designed new HD Final Cut Pro based editing systems.

Education

Full Sail University

Orlando, FL

Associate of Science in Film and Video Production

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

Charlotte, NC

Graphic Design and Multimedia

Skills